the propagandizing that's been going on for centuries now has been to try to convince the
entire world that simply because your skin is darker, you are of less value. You are of less
capability. You are of less excellence. So I say, you know what? I got to take it back.
That's what I need to do for this image. We were kings. We were kings. And so I went to my art
books and I started looking through my art books for images that would basically speak to the
context. I wanted an image of a mask and I wanted it particularly from West Africa, since we know
that so many of us are descendants of stolen people from West Africa. And I knew that I wanted it to
have some type of ancestral connection. Well, here's the every mask had an ancestral connection
because in the culture of so many tribes in Africa, I would even venture to say all. I know that's a
stretch. That's a blanket statement, but I would venture to say all. Ancestry is valuable. Ancestry
is honored. Your ancestors are an integral part of your presence and your journey.
Like you are a part of a continuance. That is what so many folks actually believe. And I believe the
same. And I believe that indigenous folks have far more of a wealth of knowledge than those of us stuck
in these matrix networks that we call cities. So I found this mask and it's called the Maiden Spirit Mask.
Agbogo Ememwo from Nigeria. Head to AmandaSeal.com and get your tickets to the live stream performance
and release of my new book, What Would the Ancestors Say, on November 8th. Also check out
When I'll Be In Your City with my book tour. See you then. Pop, pop!